让我们继续  请看着DB helper
Let's continue looking at our DB helper.
我们要填充的另一个重要函数是
The other important function that we are required to fill in
onUpdate函数
is the onUpgrade method.
这个函数在数据库已经被创建但
This function gets called when the database has already been created but
版本发生改变时被调用
the version is changed.
版本改变或者升级意味着列  表或者
A version change or upgrade should signify that the columns, tables or
数据库的一般结构已经发生改变
general structure the database has changed.
SQLiteOpenHelper能知道database版本已经发生改变
The SQLite Open Helper knows the database version has changed because
是因为我们传到它的构造函数里面的版本信息已经改变
the version we passed into its constructure has changed.
当改变数据库表的时候
Make sure to always change the database version
要确保总是改变数据库的版本
when you make changes to the database tables.
你可能会想  我为什么要关心这个
You might think, why would I care about this?
我们没有任何更新  为啥要关心这个
I'm not upgrading anything yet, so why bother?
因为 当你改变数据库表的时候
Because it's important to make sure that your application won't have
保证你的应用不发生错误非常重要
errors when you make changes to the database tables.
由于我们要用我们的数据库来作网络数据的缓存
Since we are going to be using our database as a cache for web data, and
而不用于用户产生的内容  我们会删除表
not for use generated content, we'll drop the tables,
而这将删除所有数据
which deletes all of the data.
如果数据包括用户产生的信息  当然
If the data had contained information that was user generated, of course,
我们想要保留它
we'd want to preserve it.
为了做到这一点  我们可能通过更改表来增加新列
To do that, we'd likely use alter table to add new columns.
请看指导记录
See the instructor notes for
还有关于更改表方法的更多信息  如果你对实现方法很感兴趣的话
more information on alter table if you are interested in how this is done.